question_data = [
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
            "question": "In the periodic table, Potassium's symbol is the letter K.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
            "question": "The planet Mars has two moons orbiting it.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
            "question": "The most frequent subconscious activity repeated by the human body is blinking.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
            "question": "Centripetal force is an apparent force that acts outward on a body moving around a center, arising from the body&#039;s inertia.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
            "question": "The Doppler effect applies to light.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
            "question": "The Neanderthals were a direct ancestor of modern humans.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
            "question": "Steel is an alloy of Iron and Carbon.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
            "question": "Scientists accidentally killed the once known world&#039;s oldest living creature, a mollusc, known to be aged as 507 years old.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
            "question": "Like with the Neanderthals, Homo sapiens sapiens also interbred with the Denisovans.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
            "question": "A person can get sunburned on a cloudy day.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        }
    ]


